[{"answer": "I'm just trying to live this interesting life we all have in front of us.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 25, "question": "You're a kind of fiery, emotional, soulful character, aren't you -- on and often stage?", "qSentId": 24}, {"answer": "I think at this point, I'm 51 now, I've realized, oh, it's just a journey.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 28, "question": "When you look at your extraordinary life professional and personal, how do you feel now about where you've arrived, where you are right now?", "qSentId": 27}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "You're never actually going to arrive, are you?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "Ooh.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "What's been the moment if I could replay it for you, you'd relive?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "That was 1994 unplugged, MTV.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "When was that?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "Yes, looking back on it.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "Was it as good as you always hoped?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "That's the kind of music you want to get your little Chevy, get on the, you know, I don't know the Pacific Coast highway, get the shades on, ramp up the Etheridge, isn't it?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 101, "question": "Properly in love?", "qSentId": 100}, {"answer": "Well, I -- myself was, I felt owed; they'll fill this up.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "So, before you felt that you'd been in love, but you haven't been able to give that person the whole you?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "Terribly cheesy phrase, I know.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "Have I cracked the Holy Grail of love?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "Well, it depends on how you look at it .", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "Because it's when you're the most searing, isn't it?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "Can you write good stuff if you're really happy?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "Can you?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "See, as you ask me that, this state of bliss you're talking about cannot exist without the other side, without the darker side.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "-- from the artistry of your songwriting, if I said, write, you can be in this kind of existential state of pure bliss for the next 30 years, or torment, which would produce the better music, the better songs?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "The contrast of misery, of course, is going to -- the contrast, that -- it's the desire to be out of that, into the bliss.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "What would produce the better songs?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "Having been on the journey of getting towards gay and lesbian rights, equality, understanding, diversity in America, 20 years ago, started the, you know, no, I was hoping in 10 years it would all be -- we'd all feel comfortable about it.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "Or are you still thinking, you know what, a lot of talk, not enough action?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "But do you feel that the them that is you and those who are, again, lesbian like you, are in a much better position now that you have a president prepared to go on television and say, \"I support\"?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "Tolerance, you know, I don't even like to use the word tolerance.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "Is there more tolerance?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "Because it sounds like, you know, I'm doing something that you have to tolerate.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "What's the right word?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "Especially Kansas, because I came from the Kansas in the '60s, which was the middle of the civil rights movement.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "But you feel it's getting better, even in states like Kansas?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "And what do you think is the potential prospect of a Mitt Romney presidency?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "What -- is that linked to what you said to me, that basically you've learned to love yourself?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "Yes, you can.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "But do you?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "Wow, well, I started writing when I was 10.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "What is the longest period you've ever had, where you literally couldn't write a song, of any quality at all?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "No, I don't.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "Do you get long blank periods, though?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "I was being a good grownup.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "Why did you feel that?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "If, God forbid, you were struck again by cancer, it came back or whatever, would you take marijuana?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "I want to still be creating.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "What do you want to be in five years' time?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "I've had an interesting few days.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "What are you shaking your head for?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "I feel that it is an unfair judgment and usually made from assumptions and from people who haven't read the book.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "I believe most people have the wrong idea about me, yes.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "And if so, what is is the real Rielle Hunter?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "Destroyer, villain, evil, basher.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "What do you think your public perception is right now?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "I think all of it is unfair.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "And how much of that is fair and how much of it is unfair, do you think?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "Well, the perception is based on a series of assumptions that you broke up John Edwards' marriage.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "For the public perception?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "He is responsible for his career and his marriage.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "All of it?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "I'm responsible for my part in that, being the third party.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "What are you responsible for?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "I would.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "Would you?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "I have no idea.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "Do you think this is it, no?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "It felt like the right thing at the time.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "What is the truth?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "The truth is we've had problems for a very long time that we haven't addressed because we put the children first.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "What is the truth?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "I'm -- what surprises me most is how mean people are and how much they judge based on things that they don't know anything about.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "Are you surprised?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "About me?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "I have no idea.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "Do you if it wasn't for his other children who have such strong feelings, particularly his oldest daughter who is obviously a fully fledged adult now who can make her own decisions, do you think if it wasn't for that and for their strong emotions about all this, you'd still be together?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "I have no idea.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "Does your gut feeling tell you that?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "Because you've broken up in the week that the book has come out.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "How can you say one event breaks up a relationship?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "In my life, things happen all at once.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 447, "question": "You know, obviously -- did he read the book?", "qSentId": 446}, {"answer": "UNTER: Not before publication.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "Before publication?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "Many times.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "Did you offer it to him?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "You would have to ask him that.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "Why did he say no?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "He didn't want to.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "Why did he tell you?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "He'd lived it.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "Did he try to stop you from writing it?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "You should talk to him about this.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "When did he read it?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "Well, I don't want to talk about that.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "So he has read the book?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "I want to talk about my -- yes, I do, but you can --", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "You won't talk about your book?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "The media is not entitled to everything in your life.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "What are the boundaries?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "Yes, I can read it.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "Can you read it?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "You can?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "No, I don't have those thoughts.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "Do you look back wistfully at those kind of clips and think, God, if only it could stayed like that, before anybody knew?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "Because it was fun, funny.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "Why were you smiling?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "Because you put salacious material in your book.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "Why does the media make everything so salacious?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "Oh my God.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "ORGAN: Was it or wasn't it?", "qSentId": 560}, {"answer": "You made no secret of it being the best sex of your life.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "Walked right into that one, didn't I?", "qSentId": 562}, {"answer": "I never thought of it like that.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 566, "question": "Do they?", "qSentId": 565}, {"answer": "I was talking about passive aggressive relationships, when a man doesn't stand up -- in general, relationships in general, when the man doesn't stand up, the woman is often seen as a witch on wheels, often vilified, which incidentally is exactly what has happened to me.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 579, "question": "Who was the witch on wheels?", "qSentId": 578}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "But you were obviously referring to Elizabeth, right?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "It accept it looks graceless, yes.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "Do you accept that when somebody is dead and can't answer back, it looks graceless?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "When you're in a relationship with a married man, that's how you're going to receive information about his marriage.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "So you based everything in the book that you say about her on what John Edwards told you?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "I don't know if I trust him about everything that he said.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "You don't know if you can trust him?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "I am sorry.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 620, "question": "Are you sorry for what you did to her?", "qSentId": 619}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "If she was still alive, would you say to her I'm sorry?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "Oh, I never would have gone along with that.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 637, "question": "Going back to that moment, what would you have done differently?", "qSentId": 636}, {"answer": "Out of fear.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 639, "question": "Why did you?", "qSentId": 638}, {"answer": "Not true.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 650, "question": "True?", "qSentId": 649}, {"answer": "I was devastated.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 659, "question": "When you heard him and saw him do that, what went through your mind?", "qSentId": 658}, {"answer": "I don't think he was in his right mind when he did that.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 670, "question": "ORGAN: Why did he think he could get away with it, yeah?", "qSentId": 669}, {"answer": "John told me.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 681, "question": "How did you find out, really know the truth?", "qSentId": 680}, {"answer": "Yes, feels sad.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 692, "question": "That must feel weird, doesn't it, watching that kind of clip?", "qSentId": 691}, {"answer": "Nothing went through my mind, I just felt sad.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 695, "question": "What goes through your mind?", "qSentId": 694}, {"answer": "That was a mistake.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 706, "question": "How could this end in anything but a catastrophic manner if this guy wants to be president?", "qSentId": 705}, {"answer": "That was a mistake.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 710, "question": "Whose idea was that?", "qSentId": 709}, {"answer": "That was a mistake.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 712, "question": "Whose idea was that?", "qSentId": 711}, {"answer": "I'm curious.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 714, "question": "What does it matter?", "qSentId": 713}, {"answer": "That was not true.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 721, "question": "So it was his idea?", "qSentId": 720}, {"answer": "We were both adults.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 726, "question": "Whose idea was it not to use birth control?", "qSentId": 725}, {"answer": "We were in love.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 729, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 728}, {"answer": "We weren't.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 734, "question": "Like what were you both thinking?", "qSentId": 733}, {"answer": "Clearly.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 736, "question": "At all?", "qSentId": 735}, {"answer": "I have been married before.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 738, "question": "You've been married before?", "qSentId": 737}, {"answer": "UNTER: Yes, no, I understand marriage very well.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 743, "question": "You're a marriage wrecker?", "qSentId": 742}, {"answer": "There is.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 760, "question": "I just think there's got to be a level of responsibility and self awareness, hasn't there?", "qSentId": 759}, {"answer": "I am not married.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 767, "question": "Are you responsible at all?", "qSentId": 766}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 773, "question": "But you knew he was married?", "qSentId": 772}, {"answer": "It's hard.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 781, "question": "What has that been like on a human level?", "qSentId": 780}, {"answer": "I'm responsible for the continuing on of the cover up in a big way and the continuation and the hurt and pain that came out of that.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 788, "question": "What are you responsible for?", "qSentId": 787}, {"answer": "I don't regret loving him.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 790, "question": "But you don't regret going to his hotel that night?", "qSentId": 789}, {"answer": "I do regret.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 795, "question": "Yes, but you don't regret that action of yours, as a woman who knows he's a famous guy who's married, going to his hotel room for the night, which precipitated everything else, You don't regret that?", "qSentId": 794}, {"answer": "I think that I would have edited a little differently.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 812, "question": "Given all of the publicity that the book has attracted, would you have written it a different way?", "qSentId": 811}, {"answer": "That I'm sorry for any pain that they've gone through.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 817, "question": "If John's kids are watching this, and they might well be, his daughter in particular, what would you say to her?", "qSentId": 816}, {"answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 819, "question": "Genuinely sorry?", "qSentId": 818}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120825pmt", "aSentId": 822, "question": "Are you more acutely aware, as she gets older, what you put them through?", "qSentId": 821}]